designcontest.net 2013-12-09

# Privacy | DesignContest ®

Hanei Marketing Inc. (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Company’ or ‘We’ or ‘Our’ or ‘Us’), a Delaware Corporation, owns, manages and operates DesignContest.com (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Website’). This Privacy Policy (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Policy’) informs the users (hereinafter, referred to as ‘You’ or ‘Your’) about the manner in which We collect, use, protect, and, disclose their personal and non-personal information. By accessing or using any of the features of this Website, You acknowledge that You have read, understood and agree to the provisions of this Policy.

 **Updates**

We reserve the right, in Our sole discretion, to make changes to, and update, this Policy anytime. Any substantial changes or updates to this Policy shall be notified to the registered users of the Website. However, We strongly recommend You to periodically check this page for latest updates to this Policy.

 _ **Last updated on: December 26, 2010**_

 **Information - What and How We Collect and Use?**

During the course of Your interaction with the Website, We collect some information for smooth functioning of this Website and to provide You with top-notch service quality. However, We collect only that much information as required to provide efficient, timely, reliable, and satisfactory services to the users of this Website. We do not sell, rent or otherwise commercially exploit such information of the users so collected during Your interaction with this Website, except for marketing purposes and that too after Your express consent. However, We reserve to share this information with Our affiliates, agents, and/or partners under appropriate burden of confidentiality for administrative reasons.

Personal Information: When You fill out the online registration form to join the Website, We collect certain personal details including, without limitation, Your full name, email address, postal address, telephone number, fax, profile, preferred username, etc. This information is primarily used to contact You to confirm and verify, to inform You about Your account activity, to inform You about the contest(s) that match Your profile, or any other matter that We think deserves to be informed about. Such miscellaneous matters include, without limitation, resolving disputes, providing customer support, troubleshooting, managing payments to and from the Website, and enforcing Our Terms of Service Agreement and other legal policies regarding Your use of this Website. We may also use Your email address to send newsletters, updates, and news from the Website. However, You are free to opt-out of the mailing list by managing Your account.

Non-Personal Information: While You are accessing, browsing, and/or using this Website in any capacity – member or non-member – We also collect certain non-personal information. This information is in the form of usage statistics and includes, without limitation, Your Internet Protocol (IP) Address, Your browser-type & version, the operating system installed on Your computer, Your Internet Service Provider’s (ISP’s) IP Address, the time-stamp of Your visit, etc. This non-personal information is used to enhance Your browsing experience of this Website, improve Website and system administration, conduct internal research, compile and provide statistical data to the advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements. 

**Cookies – How and Why We Use Them?**

In order to collect non-personal information, We use cookies, which are small text files placed on the hard drive of Your computer system. We use harmless cookies to enhance Your Website browsing experience. Primarily, cookies are used to save Your session details and avoid multiple log-in during the same session. When You sign out of Your account, all the cookies so deposited by this Website on Your computer system shall be cleared.

 **Spam Policy**

We have a zero-tolerance for spam. Resultantly, We do not send any unsolicited commercial or non-commercial email to You or any of Your referred friends. You can further control the kind of communications You receive from Us by managing Your account.

 **Do We Share Any of Your Information with Other Users of Website?**

Some details of Your personal profile including, without limitation, Your name, business name, area of expertise, etc., will be shared with other users of this Website. This feature is enabled so that the users can make an informed decision whether or not to conduct business with You. Your feedback ratings and comments by other users will also be publicly accessible.

 **Third Party Links**

This Website may contain links to third party websites belonging to affiliates, partners, agents, and advertisers. We disclaim any responsibility for such links since We do not control or monitor the privacy practices of the linked websites. If You visit these linked websites and transact with them, You do so at Your own sole risk. All such use of the linked websites shall be subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of those websites.

 **Information – How We Secure It?**

Your personal information, including the information collected for processing of payment, is stored and preserved on the third party servers, which are subject to the strictest safety codes as prevalent in the industry. Generally, SSL-encryption technology is used to preserve all the sensitive data, the compromise on which could seriously endanger Your privacy. Additionally, We also employ several human and technological security measures at multiple levels in order to preserve Your personal as well as financial information. However, technology can never be fool-proof. Therefore, We disclaim any liability arising out of any loss to anyone due to unauthorized access to Our servers.

 **Information – Disclosure Disclaimers**

The Company shall not be liable for the disclosure of any of Your information so collected under any of the following circumstances:

1.    Disclosure to the government agencies in response to legal processes, like subpoena; or  
2.    Any unlawful access to, and transmissions of, information from the Website; or  
3.    Disclosure of personal information by You on any online and offline media including, without limitation, blogs, social networking websites, forums, message boards, etc.  
4.    Disclosure of information to the successor of the Website in the event of sale of DesignContest.com

 **Any Questions?**

If You still have any questions on the privacy of Your information, feel free to contact us. We’ll respond to all the queries promptly and appropriately.
